<data>
  <s udid="n01012003">
    <switchcase lang="en">First one of the Yazidi women started crying, then one of her friends.</switchcase>
    <switchcase lang="uk">Спочатку одна єзидка почала плакати, потім хтось з її подруг.</switchcase>
  </s>
  <s udid="w01142031">
    <switchcase lang="en">John of Gaunt died in 1399.</switchcase>
    <switchcase lang="uk">Іоан Гентський помер у 1399.</switchcase>
  </s>
  <s udid="n01006011">
    <switchcase lang="en">A witness told police that the victim had attacked the suspect in April.</switchcase>
    <switchcase lang="uk">Свідок повідомив поліції, що потерпілий скоїв напад на підозрюваного ще у квітні.</switchcase>
  </s>
  <s udid="n01007012">
    <switchcase lang="en">There are parallels to draw here between games and our everyday lives.</switchcase>
    <switchcase lang="uk">Тут можна провести паралелі між іграми і нашим повсякденним життям.</switchcase>
  </s>
  <s udid="n01009054">
    <switchcase lang="en">“We’ve requested other nations to help us populate the zoo with different species of animals, including a pig,” Saqib said.</switchcase>
    <switchcase lang="uk">„Ми попросили інші країни допомогти нам заселити зоопарк різними видами тварин, включаючи свиней“ — каже Сакіб.</switchcase>
  </s>
  <s udid="n01011017">
    <switchcase lang="en">"I'm going to jail either way, hope it was worth it."</switchcase>
    <switchcase lang="uk">„Всеодно я потраплю до в'язниці, сподіваюсь воно було того варте“.</switchcase>
  </s>
  <s udid="n01016032">
    <switchcase lang="en">The Mate 9 phones lack an artificial intelligence interface, like the Google Assistant or Apple's Siri.</switchcase>
    <switchcase lang="uk">Телефонам Мейт-9 бракувало штучноінтелектуального інтерфейса, як-от Гугл-помічник або Еплівський Сірі.</switchcase>
  </s>
  <s udid="n01027007">
    <switchcase lang="en">Who are they?</switchcase>
    <switchcase lang="uk">Хто вони?</switchcase>
  </s>
  <s udid="n01029007">
    <switchcase lang="en">A keen guitarist, he played a concert there the same year.</switchcase>
    <switchcase lang="uk">Завзятий гітарист, він грав там концерт того ж року.</switchcase>
  </s>
  <s udid="n01029006">
    <switchcase lang="en">Seagal made headlines when he described Russia's actions in Crimea, which it annexed in 2014, as "very reasonable".</switchcase>
    <switchcase lang="uk">Сігал потрапив у газетні заголовки, коли описав дії Росії в Криму, який вона анексувала у 2014 році, як "дуже резонні".</switchcase>
  </s>
  <s udid="n01052004">
    <switchcase lang="en">She was 84 years old.</switchcase>
    <switchcase lang="uk">Їй було 84 роки.</switchcase>
  </s>
  <s udid="n01087035">
    <switchcase lang="en">“I loved the tropical colours,” he says.</switchcase>
    <switchcase lang="uk">„Мені сподобались тропічні кольори“, каже він.</switchcase>
  </s>
  <s udid="n01132006">
    <switchcase lang="en">It's the election, of course, not "Game of Thrones."</switchcase>
    <switchcase lang="uk">Звісно, це вибори, а не „Ігри престолів“.</switchcase>
  </s>
  <s udid="n01147087">
    <switchcase lang="en">For anyone who wants to see the capital in all its glory, November's a great time to go.</switchcase>
    <switchcase lang="uk">Для тих, хто хоче побачити столицю у всій свої красі, листопад — саме час туди поїхати.</switchcase>
  </s>
  <s udid="w01002075">
    <switchcase lang="en">The 2019 Winter Universiade will be hosted by Krasnoyarsk.</switchcase>
    <switchcase lang="uk">Зимова універсіада 2019 проходитиме в Красноярську.</switchcase>
  </s>
  <s udid="w01003051">
    <switchcase lang="en">Examples are the Line Islands in the Pacific and the Maldives in the Indian Ocean.</switchcase>
    <switchcase lang="uk">Приклади — Острови Лайн у Тихому океані та Мальдіви в Індійському.</switchcase>
  </s>
  <s udid="w01003056">
    <switchcase lang="en">Granite islands include Seychelles and Tioman and volcanic islands such as Saint Helena.</switchcase>
    <switchcase lang="uk">До гранітових островів заносять Сейшели і Тіоман та вулканічні острови, як от острів Святої Гелени.</switchcase>
  </s>
  <s udid="w01014002">
    <switchcase lang="en">The northern portion of the Caucasus is known as the Ciscaucasus and the southern portion as the Transcaucasus.</switchcase>
    <switchcase lang="uk">Північна частина Кавказу зветься Передкавказзя, а південна частистина — Закавказзя.</switchcase>
  </s>
  <s udid="w01026037">
    <switchcase lang="en">The greater part of the Danube Delta lies in Romania (Tulcea county), while its northern part, on the left bank of the Chilia arm, is situated in Ukraine (Odessa Oblast).</switchcase>
    <switchcase lang="uk">Більша частина дельти Дунаю лежить в Румунії (Тульчанський повіт), а її північна частина, що на лівому березі Кілійського рукава, міститься в Україні (Одеська область).</switchcase>
  </s>
  <s udid="w01029083">
    <switchcase lang="en">Christian churches in northwestern Europe and Ukraine often used willow branches in place of palms in the ceremonies on Palm Sunday.</switchcase>
    <switchcase lang="uk">Християнські церкви в північно-західній Європі та Україні для церемоній на Пальмову неділю часто використовували вербові гілки замість пальмових.</switchcase>
  </s>
  <s udid="w01127071">
    <switchcase lang="en">Her 1981 album Wild West was one of her biggest sellers.</switchcase>
    <switchcase lang="uk">Її альбом Wild West 1981 року був одним з найбільш продаваних.</switchcase>
  </s>
  <s udid="w01148068">
    <switchcase lang="en">This time it reached him, but he refused to believe that she no longer wanted to be married to him.</switchcase>
    <switchcase lang="uk">Цього разу він до нього дійшов, але він відмовився повірити, що вона більше не хоче бути його дружиною.</switchcase>
  </s>
  <s udid="w01149002">
    <switchcase lang="en">Wright was born in Poole, Dorset, but grew up predominantly in Wells, Somerset.</switchcase>
    <switchcase lang="uk">Райт народився в Пулі, графство Дорсет, але ріс переважно у Велсі, графство Сомерсет.</switchcase>
  </s>
  <s udid="w01150044">
    <switchcase lang="en">The Great Powers did not fulfill the requests for recognition of Albania.</switchcase>
    <switchcase lang="uk">Великі держави не задовільнили прохання визнати Албанію.</switchcase>
  </s>
  <s udid="w01150045">
    <switchcase lang="en">At the beginning of the London conference in December 1912 the ambassadors of all six Great Powers rejected the plan for establishing an independent Albania.</switchcase>
    <switchcase lang="uk">На початку Лондонської конференції у грудні 1912-го посли всіх шести Великих держав відхилили план з урядження незалежної Албанії.</switchcase>
  </s>
</data>
<!--

(\w+) (.*)\n\1 (.*)
<sb id="$1"/><s udid="$1"><switchcase lang="en">$2</switchcase><switchcase lang="uk">$3</switchcase></s>


-->
